Sir's son, where are you, aunt, I
feel like it in the morning,
yes tell me the news, the news is fine, the
news is fine, I am fine,
you are not improving anything in the greenery of Kathmandu, oh oh, I am
improving myself, father, my voice is
falling,
how far are you going, take me from Kathmandu to a
brothel in the alley,
you are a broker of brothels, there is a room
in my youth, father, go to the brothel,
how are you,
first I am a straight
brother, dishonesty, since then I am in the
alley, in the alley, I am going to the
restroom, listen, I have tea, I want
tea,
six months in Kathmandu,
Koteshwar Josh, at
12 o'clock in the night, I will go to the toilet, listen
[Music]
tell me, first there is poverty in Kathmandu, make
concrete houses all around, make bamboo houses in the middle,
tea must be cheap in here
[Music]
tell me, a very poor man should open a shop, tie the
lights, put a mirror and stay there,
drink tea, do good to the poor,
uncle,
baba, if you take my head, you are
in the wrong place, uncle, get up, go to the
hotel  So book in school
uncle, no hotel,
yes uncle, where can you help me, if we help you, then we will help you,
four people from
our village, you help me,
bring tea once, listen AB, I will buy a beedi, if we don't get
beedis, then go to the shop, if we do
n't get beedis, then we will make
potato chips in between the rotis, [Music]
take it, give it to me
later, I am
standing there,
[Music]
hey listen,
where is the sugar, I want to go, if there is
sugar, then sugar, when I drink it myself, then
why don't I make my tea, if you
need more sugar, please ask me
uncle, Billa, we
put paper on everything, I am a village
man, see the old man's salary, get
paper on everything,
cut it and take it,
uncle, it is 120 rupees,
add it in the room,
uncle, if you give me tea, I will
ask for milk for tea from Birgan,
yes, sugar
from China,
yes,
ask for tea leaves from Ram, then go and make
tea for
20 rupees, we have a dozen people in the PM Bal shop, the
old one,
give tea in a glass, take it, cut it and bring it, do
n't ask uncle, and sit for tea, it is 120 rupees for tea
₹120
[Music]
Hey, just ride me,
take my money
[Music]
I'll
ask for
20 for tea, 20 [Music]
Come on, do
n't leave me, hold my hand and hit me,
Kathmandu,
Kathmandi, if you
hold my hand, you'll cut my hand, you'll beat me, you'll get
unconscious medicine in the tea, I don't fall unconscious,
this is what I felt, listen, we are from the village, Bhava Panchu, father has a
different fight, Panchu father has BP in one hand, he has a
doctor in the other hand, he presses the
tractor with his hand, he has to ride the tractor, he is
in the hospital for five months, listen to five things,
remember, from the hospital, it's a
very bad work, hey,
without any reason, it's a
very bad work,
you tell me, tell me, which bad work,
take me to the room, uncle,
spit in the uncle's mouth,
go and see in the toilet,
oh my god
[Music]
what is the habit in the toilet,
we
all men sprinkle water in the house, throw it out
in the house, Tomandu,
don't close the house, don't understand, is it
okay, make tea  I want you to
drink tea,
yes
then I have to eat the Khani Beedi and throw it at the gate.
Uncle,
you eat the Khani Beedi at the gate, do
n't throw the garbage at the gate, throw it at the
head, son, I am here, you understand,
listen, listen, I am an educated father, till date
I want you to
drink tea, forget about it, don't
make a video call on the mobile.
Ok.
[Music]
Uncle, I will never forget your kindness throughout my life,
now what do I say?